Guide to the Records of WNYU RG.39.5
New York University Archives
Records of WNYU
1949-1996
1949-1996, 2013-ongoing
New York University Archives
WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.)
RG.39.5
23 Linear Feet in 14 record cartons, 10 manuscript boxes, 3 LP boxes, and 1 CD box.
6 websites in 6 archived websites.
This collection documents WNYU's history from 1949-1992, from its inception as an educational AM radio station to its acquisition of an FM frequency and emergence as innovative music programming. Administrative files, audio recordings of broadcasts, publications, and architectural drawings situate WNYU's growth and impact within NYU, New York City, and music history. The administrative files in this collection date from 1949-1969 and include correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, and subject files that portray the efforts of WNYU's staff to build up an AM-FM radio station and maintain educational programming in the New York metropolitan area. The audio recordings in this collection document WNYU's FM programming from 1973-1992, which highlighted music of various genres from the 1960s-1990s. Listeners could hear DJ sets, live performances, and interviews with musicians in shows such as the New Afternoon Show, Crucial Chaos, Club 89, and Music View, among others. A few recordings in this collection also highlight NYU events and lecture series. This collection also contains architectural drawings of the WNYU radio station and publications of WNYU, including newspapers published from 1957-1973 and Static program guides published from 1986-1988.
Arrangement
This collection has been organized into five series:
Series I. Administrative Files
Series II. Drawings
Series III. Publications
Series IV. Subject Files
Series V. Recorded Programs
Series VI. Archived Websites
Scope and Contents
This collection documents WNYU's history from 1949-1992, from its inception as an educational AM radio station to its acquisition of an FM frequency and emergence as innovative music programming. Administrative files, audio recordings of broadcasts, publications, and architectural drawings situate WNYU's growth and impact within NYU, New York City, and music history.
The administrative files in this collection date from 1949-1969 and include correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, and subject files that portray the efforts of WNYU's staff to build up an AM-FM radio station and maintain educational programming in the New York metropolitan area. Correspondence is predominantly between WNYU's staff and other constituent parts of the University, including Joseph Steinberg, the station's manager during the 1960s with University offices; the Inter-Colligiate Broadcasting System; Miller, Montgomery and Spanding concerning construction for WNYU facilities; and Larry J. Hollander, the faculty advisor to the WYNU staff, with Steinberg. Other correspondence relates to the broader media and metropolitan community, such as correspondence of the staff with fellow radio stations including the Columbia University station, concerning such topics as the election of 1964, Ray Nelson, and a Senator Claiborne Pell interview about youth legislation; letters from The New York Times to Arnold Rosner, Director of Classical Music at WNYU; letters from the Police Department of New York City; and letters from United Press International. Also included are minutes of meetings of the WNYU Board of Directors, budget reports and operating expense estimates of WNYU members, log forms, schedules, applications, architectural drawings, certificates from Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company, advertising brochures, programs, newsletters, printed promotional material, newspapers published from 1957-1973, and Static programs published from 1986-1988.
The audio recordings in this collection document WNYU's FM programming from 1973-1992, which highlighted music of various genres from the 1960s-1990s with an emphasis on punk and underground scenes. Shows included the New Afternoon Show, Crucial Chaos, Club 89, Music View, Rap This!, and Unheard, among others. Live performances and interviews with musicians and groups such as Sonic Youth, the Dead Kennedys, the Smashing Pumpkins, K.D. Lang, LL Cool J, Band of Susans, Butthole Surfers, Frank Zappa, and Sarah McLaughlin were showcased between DJ sets. The New Midnight Society provided a platform for NYU students and faculty to read their written works and showcase musical compositions. A few recordings in this collection also highlight NYU events and lecture series.
Historical Note
WNYU was formed in 1949 on the University Heights campus of New York University by a group of engineers. Initially, the station only broadcast to the University Heights cafeteria. Well established by 1956, WNYU became a member of the Inter-Collegiate Broadcasting System (IBS). In 1955 the radio division of the Television, Motion Picture and Radio Department of the Communications Arts Group started a closed circuit station, WCAG, at the Washington Square Campus. In 1963 WNYU (Heights Station) and WCAG (Washington Square Station) merged into one closed circuit radio station through the use of a telephone cable. It was decided that WCAG would broadcast to both campuses during the day while WNYU would take over in the evenings. This continued until 1973, when NYU sold the University Heights campus. At that time the equipment was brought to Loeb Student Center on Washington Square. During the period of 1965-1973 the station worked to acquire an FM frequency. In 1965 NYU made an agreement with the United Nations to use their channel, "206." NYU submitted their first application to the Federal Communication Commission (FCC) in 1965. After three years the FCC decided that channel "206" should be shared by NYU and Fairleigh Dickinson University of New Jersey. WNYU broadcast from 4 p.m. to 1 a.m. on weekdays.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Custodial History
The records of WNYU Radio Station were transferred to the New York University Archives when the radio station was moved from Gould Memorial Library at the University Heights campus to Loeb Student Center on Washington Square in June 1973. Further accretions to the collection have been added in the intervening years.
http://wnyu.org/, http://wnyustatic.tumblr.com/, https://orgsync.com/63665/chapter/, https://www.facebook.com/wnyuradio, and http://earshotwnyu.wordpress.com/wnyu-radio/ were selected by Aleksandr Gelfand in 2013-2014 as part of the RG 39: Student Organizations and Publications Web Archive using Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. In June 2023, https://staticmag.org/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2023.034.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact University Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Take Down Policy
Archived websites are made accessible for purposes of education and research. NYU Libraries have given attribution to rights holders when possible; however, due to the nature of archival collections, we are not always able to identify this information.
If you hold the rights to materials in our archived websites that are unattributed, please let us know so that we may maintain accurate information about these materials.
If you are a rights holder and are concerned that you have found material on this website for which you have not granted permission (or is not covered by a copyright exception under US copyright laws), you may request the removal of the material from our site by submitting a notice, with the elements described below, to the special.collections@nyu.edu.
Please include the following in your notice: Identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; your contact information, such as an address, telephone number, and email address; a statement that you are the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed and that you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and made under penalty of perjury; and your physical or electronic signature. Upon receiving a notice that includes the details listed above, we will remove the allegedly infringing material from public view while we assess the issues identified in your notice.
Radio in education.; Radio broadcasting -- Rules and regulations.; Radio broadcasting -- Management; Radio broadcasting -- History; Radio broadcasting -- Archival resources.; Radio -- Equipment and supplies.; Architectural drawings (visual works); Job applications.; Newsletters.; Minutes (administrative records); Petitions.; Advertisements; Punk rock music.; Alternative rock music.; Rock music -- 1981-1990.; Radio and music; Musical performance.; Hollander, Larry J.; Fairleigh Dickinson University -- Radio broadcasting; Columbia University -- Radio broadcasting; Nelson, Ray; Miller, Montgomery & Spanding; Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company; Inter-Collegiate Broadcasting System; New York University -- Radio broadcasting; New York University. Communication Arts Group; New York (N.Y.). Police Department; New York Times Company; Steinberg, Joseph; United Nations; Pell, Claiborne, 1918-2009; Rosner, Arnold, 1945-; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); United Press International; WCAG (Radio station: New York, N.Y.)
- Series I: Administrative Files, 1949-1969
  Arrangement
  Series I. Administrative Files is arranged chronologically.
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Nov. 29, 1949 -April 8, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Feb. 17, 1955 -Dec. 27, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, 1955-1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Nov. 28, 1956 -May 7, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Dec. 9, 1957 -Sept. 23, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Jan. 5, 1958 -Mar. 18, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Jan. 29, 1960 -Nov. 15, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Oral history interview by Blair Schomaker, Undated; Schomaker, Blair (Box 1, Folder 7, Cassette 1)
      Scope and contents
      This recording contains an interview with an unnamed male, made for the NYU Archives, about the history and establishment of WNYU.
      Original format
      90-minute Memorex audio cassette
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Apr. 20, 1960 -Feb. 27, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Jan. 8, 1962 -Nov. 12, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Mar. 1, 1963 -Dec. 6, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Mar. 1, 1963 -Dec. 6, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Apr. 3, 1963 -May 14, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Oct. 7, 1963 -Dec. 6, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Aug. 10, 1964-May 25, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Oct. 11, 1964 -May 12, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Nov. 5, 1964 -Mar. 11, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Dec. 14, 1964 -Apr. 18, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Feb. 21, 1964 -Jun. 15, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Jan. 12, 1965 -Dec. 18, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Apr. 29, 1965 -Sept. 22, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Aug. 31, 1965 -May 16, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Oct. 14, 1965 -Oct. 19, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Nov. 18, 1965 -Apr. 19, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Radio Station WFDU, 1965 -1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Convention, 1965 -1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Jan. 17, 1966-Aug. 15, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Feb. 21, 1966 -Oct. 31, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Nov. 22, 1966 -Apr. 18, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Jan. 17, 1967 -Dec. 4, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Apr. 6, 1967 -Jun. 6, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Jun. 17, 1968 -Dec. 20, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, minutes, legal documents, memoranda, Jan. 6, 1969 -Feb. 6, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Reports, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - WNYU log forms, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Series II: Drawings, Undated
  Series II. Drawings is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Drawings of WNYU radio station, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Drawings of WNYU radio station, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Series III: Publications, 1957-1988
  Series III. Publications is arranged alphabetically by material type.
  - Newspapers, February, 1967 - May, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers, January, 1957 - October, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Printed material, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Printed material, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Static Program Guides, 1986-1988 (Box Shared University Archives 081, Folder 1, 2)
- Series IV: Subject Files, 1967-1981
  Series IV. Subject Files is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Advisors, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Arbitron, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - (FCC) Docket No. 17454 File No. BPED-742, Docket No. 17455 File No. BPED-751 - Vol. I, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - (FCC) Docket No. 17454 File No. BPED-742, Docket No. 17455 File No. BPED-751 - Vol. II (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - (FCC) Docket No. 17454 File No. BPED-742, Docket No. 17455 File No. BPED-751 - Reply, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Engineering, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - FCC Permit & License Copies, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Graduates: Personnel Questionnaires, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Inactive Personnel, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Legal- Wilner & Scheiner, 1971-1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Legal-FCC agreement with FDU, 1972-1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Maggin, Jane (Director of Student Affairs, WNYU Advisor), 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Management Committee Meeting Minutes, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Management & Staff Meetings, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - News Stylebook, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Operations, 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Policy (By Laws)- Folder 1 of 2, 1967-1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Policy (By Laws)- Folder 2 of 2, 1967-1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Press, 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Program Highlights, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Program Highlights, 1974-1981 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Program Material, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Programming- Folder 1 of 2, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Programming- Folder 2 of 2, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Programming, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Programming, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Publicity & Promotion- Folder 1 of 2, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Publicity & Promotion- Folder 2 of 2, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Reports, Agenda, Staff Questionnaires, 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Share-Time Agreement WFDU/WNYU, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Staff Questionnaire, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - STL (Studio-Transmitter Link), 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Ultra-Violet, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Series V: Recorded Programs, 1968-1996; 20 Linear Feet in 14 record cartons, 3 LP boxes, 2 manuscript boxes, and 1 CD box.
  Series V. Recorded Programs is arranged alphabetically by the title of the show and chronologically by episode recording date; unattributed and undated episodes can be found at the end of the list.
  Scope and Contents
  The audio recordings in this collection document WNYU's FM programming from 1973-1992, which highlighted music of various genres from the 1960s-1990s with an emphasis on punk and underground scenes. Shows included the New Afternoon Show, Crucial Chaos, Club 89, Music View, Rap This!, and Unheard, among others. Live performances and interviews with musicians and groups such as Sonic Youth, the Dead Kennedys, the Smashing Pumpkins, K.D. Lang, LL Cool J, Band of Susans, Butthole Surfers, Frank Zappa, and Sarah McLaughlin were showcased between DJ sets. The New Midnight Society provided a platform for NYU students and faculty to read their written works and showcase musical compositions. A few recordings in this collection also highlight NYU events and lecture series.
  - Program Logs and Notes, circa 1970-1996 (Box Shared University Archives 081, Folder 3)
  - Backroads: Sean Grissom (Live), circa 1986 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0129)
  - Backroads: True West, June 22, 1987 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0652)
  - Backroads: Dave Alvin, September 28, 1987 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0546)
  - Backroads: Roger Manning, November 16, 1987 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0608)
  - Backroads: Chris Stamey (Live), November 30, 1987 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0654)
  - Backroads: Stealin' Horses, April 18, 1988 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0127)
  - Club 89: Vaughan Mason (Interview), May 12, 1987 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0555)
    The host of this episode is Leigh Lust.
  - Club 89, September 29, 1987 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0345)
  - Club 89, December 16, 1987 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0181)
  - Club 89 with Sonya Baines, December 17, 1987 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0175)
  - Club 89: Ultramagnetic M.C.'s (Live Set), February 13, 1988 (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0101)
  - Club 89: Jose Chinga (Interview), The Lord Shafiqy (Live Rap), April 7, 1988 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0602)
    The host of this episode is Chris Cullen.
  - Club 89: Carolyn Harding and Mike Anthony, April 27, 1988 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0603)
  - Club 89: Devo (Interview), June 7, 1988 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0535, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0385)
  - Club 89: Ultramagnetic MCs (Live), February 13, 1989 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0514)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Duration: 00:30:00
  - Club 89: Wire (Interview), June 1, 1989 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0500)
    Duration: 00:25:47
    The host of this episode is Hugh Foley.
  - Club 89: The Chosen Ones (Interview), August 14, 1989 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0342)
  - Club 89: King Tee (Interview), October 30, 1990 (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0113)
    The host of this episode is Ray Rosario.
  - Club 89, Undated (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0353)
  - Club 89, Undated (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0401)
    Duration: 00:12:09
  - Club 89: Doug E. Fresh with Beatbox, Undated (Box 16, Fidelipac 39_5_0194)
  - Club 89: The Chosen Ones, Undated (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0344)
  - Crucial Chaos: Tommy Stupid, November 20, 1980 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0645)
  - Crucial Chaos: World Made Flesh (Live), April 2, 1985 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0668)
  - Crucial Chaos: Murphy's Law (Interview), October 16, 1986 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0331)
  - Crucial Chaos: Youth of Today, October 30, 1986 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0329)
  - Crucial Chaos: Ludichrist, November 20, 1986 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0010)
  - Crucial Chaos: 7 Seconds, November 26, 1986 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0321)
  - Crucial Chaos: A.O.D., December 11, 1986 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0628)
  - Crucial Chaos: Token Entry, January 1, 1987 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0644)
  - Crucial Chaos: Target 19 (Live), January 14, 1987 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0646)
  - Crucial Chaos: Straight Ahead, February 26, 1987 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0284)
  - Crucial Chaos: Youth Defense League, March 5, 1987 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0611)
  - Crucial Chaos: Police DNC, April 9, 1987 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0074)
  - Crucial Chaos: Altercation (Interview), April 16, 1987 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0539)
    Audio reel 39_5_0539 was identified as moldy in December, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, contact the Preservation Department immediately. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - Crucial Chaos: PMS, May 7, 1987 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0244)
  - Crucial Chaos: Rest in Pieces, May 21, 1987 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0632)
  - Crucial Chaos: Prong (Interview), May 28, 1987 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0264)
  - Crucial Chaos: Underdog (Live), June 11, 1987 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0340, 39_5_0341)
  - Crucial Chaos: Sacred Denial, July 2, 1987 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0120, 39_5_0125)
  - Crucial Chaos: Sand in the Face, July 16, 1987 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0124, Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0231, Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0612)
  - Crucial Chaos: Side by Side (Live), July 30, 1987 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0234)
  - Crucial Chaos: Uncertain (Live), September 3, 1987 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0664)
  - Crucial Chaos: Social Decay, October 8, 1987 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0072)
  - Crucial Chaos: Trip Six (Live), October 29, 1987 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0640, 39_5_0643)
  - Crucial Chaos: NY Hoods (Live), November 11, 1987 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0243)
  - Crucial Chaos: GBH (Live), November 12, 1987 (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0093)
  - Crucial Chaos: Mental Abuse (Live), November 19, 1987 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0187)
  - Crucial Chaos: Aware (Live), November 26, 1987 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0520, 39_5_0526)
  - Crucial Chaos: Doggy Style and D.I. (Live), December 3, 1987 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0227, 39_5_0249, Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0615)
  - Crucial Chaos: Six and Violence (Live), Ludichrist (Interview), December 10, 1987 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0258, 39_5_0260, 39_5_0261)
  - Crucial Chaos: Stand Proud (Live), January 5, 1988 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0287)
  - Crucial Chaos: Zombie Squad (Live), January 21, 1988 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0076)
  - Crucial Chaos: Occupied Territory (Live Performance), February 11, 1988 (Box 10, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0003)